Alejandro Munoz

0414 822 270

alej.munoz@protonmail.com

github.com/rtxd

Career Objective

I am a final year Bachelor of Science in Information and Technology student. I have a passion for working closely in teams to develop software. I would love a position that allows me to develop the skills and experience I have received from university and apply them in a real work environment.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology and Diploma in Information Technology Professional Practice University of Technology Sydney 2017 - Present

Certificate II in Information, Digital Media and Technology Academy of Interactive Entertainment

2014

Marcellin College Randwick

2011 - 2016

 Received the Champagnat Award which is present to students who are recognised as role models within the college community.

Employment

PixateMe

November 2019 – Current

Web Developer

- Setup and designed a complete shopify store: pixateme.com
- Developed a small program in Node JS that gets a Minecraft skin and puts it onto a Onesie pattern ready for printing.

Cloomein Pty Ltd

September 2018 – February 2020

Co-Founder of Cloomein

- Co-Founded Cloomein, a company that developed applications to help increase customer service for businesses.
- Developed an application called InTouch which is an easy and effective way to keep customers up to date with progress on the service a business provides, whilst simultaneously giving you feedback on how they feel each step of the way
- Developed InTouch progressive mobile website in React Redux with Node JS, Express and MySQL

- Designed and developed responsive pages using Material UI and Google design documentation
- Created backend database and API Endpoints using Express
- Create Cloomein Wordpress site: cloomein.com

SkyZone Alexandria

January 2018 - August 2018

Party Host

SkyWriter Tech Pty Ltd

June 2017 – July 2017

Junior Software Developer

 Helped create a proof of concept application that used DevExpress Technology to generate an interactive report within a webpage.

WiseTech Global Pty. Ltd.

July 2014

Work Experience

- Translogix Systems Transport Logistics Software
- Developed software written in C# and SQL which retrieved data from an external database, hosted on a server, and then displayed the data.

Extracurricular Activities

Participated in University of New South Wales ProgComp

June 2014

The Software Development Studio UTS

July 2017 - October 2017

- Developed a web-based solution for the global company Ericsson
- Solution involved use google map APIs to create optimised routes for workers to follow and to allow data analysts to pick up any discrepancies in data easily.
- Team worked in Angular 1 to further develop the project and successfully met the requirements that were given to us.
- The project was worked on with two-week sprints on top of University classes and study.

Secretary of the Programmers' Society UTS

November 2017 - November 2018

Helped run and organise:

- WiseTech Global sponsored Hackathon
- Programming Competition
- VR Night
- Arduino workshop collaboration with other societies

Transferable Skills

Planning and Organisational Skills

As the secretary of the Programmers' Society I had to Plan and Organise several events that we hosted. All these events were considered successful and raised the amount of memberships within the Programmers' Society.

Teamwork

My ability to collaborate and coordinate as a team. This has been demonstrated through my work in the Software Development Project subject which we had to work in small efficient teams of 5 to completely develop a piece of software. Also demonstrated through my role as secretary for the Programmers' Society.

Entrepreneurship

I have experience with setting up and running businesses. My first start-up company was a tech start-up by the name of Cloomein. I co-founded Cloomein with two other colleagues and worked on it for 2 years. The second start-up I worked on is called PixateMe, I had an idea that I thought might have a chance and took a shot.

Technical Skills

Languages: C#, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Python, SQL, JavaScript, Node JS, React JS, Redux, Express JS, MySQL, MS SQL Express

- Experience using AWS to set up an RDS instance, S3 Bucket and EC2 instances.

Engines: Unity, MonoGame

Referees

Available upon request